{
    "id": "b8b67627d7904cafa98f6ee745c55098",
    "title": "Like and as",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "3e731a74c070489fbaa688d2d4db0a6d",
            "title": "Like And As",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She behaves …………………. a spoilt brat.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "A crocodile starts life …………………. an egg.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "like"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He drinks …………………. a fish.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Nobody loves her ……………….. I do.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "like"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was an alcoholic, ……………….. were most of his friends.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "like"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why do you behave ………………… a child?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He worked …………………. a waiter for two years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She looks ……………….. her sister.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is quite good at scientific subjects ………………….. physics and chemistry.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He will do it, …………………. agreed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}